capitalgroup.com 2019-03-26

# Privacy | Capital Group

### Important Legal Information

Certain companies within The Capital Group Companies offer a number of products and services designed specifically for various types of investors in various countries and regions. These products or services are only offered to such investors in those countries and regions in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. This web site is for information purposes only and should not be construed as an offer to sell, a solicitation to buy, or a recommendation for any security, or as an offer to provide advisory or other services in any jurisdiction in which such offer, solicitation, purchase, or sale would be unlawful under the securities laws of such jurisdiction.

### Privacy Policy - Job Applicants

#### A. INTRODUCTION

The Capital Group is committed to ensuring the privacy of your "Personal Information" (the identifiable information about you which you provide to us as an applicant for a position with Capital). Your Personal Information will be used for recruitment purposes and protected in accordance with these Guidelines.

These Guidelines may be amended by the Capital Group from time to time.

These Guidelines will not form part of any contract of employment offered to successful candidates.

#### B. DISCLOSURE WITHIN THE CAPITAL GROUP COMPANIES

To enable the Capital Group to act as an integrated global business, your Personal Information may be transferred to Capital-affiliated companies outside the country where you reside, including to companies in countries where your privacy rights may not be protected as extensively as in your home country. We will, however, endeavor to ensure that adequate security measures are taken.

#### C. SECURITY

The Capital Group seeks to ensure adequate security to protect processing of Personal Information and to prevent its misuse.

The Capital Group also ensures that third parties processing Personal Information on its behalf take adequate security measures.

#### D. ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION

If your Personal Information is held in an electronic database, you have the right to see the Personal Information that the Capital Group holds about you. If you would like to view or correct your Personal Information, discuss the outcome of your job application, withdraw your consent or if you have any questions about these Guidelines, you should send a request in writing to:  

Personal Information will be kept for a reasonable period of time, and the Capital Group will allow you to view your Personal Information upon reasonable notice and at reasonable times. Personal Information will be retained in accordance with the relevant legal requirements.

#### E. YOUR RESPONSIBILITY

The Capital Group makes reasonable efforts to ensure the accuracy of Personal Information, but you are requested to ensure that your Personal Information is kept up to date and to amend any inaccuracies.
